

TIMUR ADAMOV

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

**** 7473673375

adamoffgroup@gmail.com

7473673375

in Timur Adamov

@justintimurlake

12147 Magnolia Blvd

SKILLS

HTML
CSS
JS
FIGMA
PHOTOSHOP
EXEL
DATABASE
MANAGEMENT

CONTACTS OF PREVIOUS JOBS

A&T

REACT

+79884079999

Primavera@mail.ru

ARIAN

+79882355532

starigrad123@yandex.ru

ADAMOFFGROUP

**** +1747367<u>3375</u>

adamoffgroup@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Working as a web developer for me it is unlike any other job. It is a chance to discover new languages, such as JS, React, TypeScript, Python. However, working as a web developer, it is not all about code, it is more about problem solving.

I have more than 1 years of experience working in IT. The knowledge which I brought is unique, because it give me opportunity to make every project unique for client.

EXPERIENCE

T&K

06/2018 - 08/2018

ARIAN

03/2020 - 06/2020

ADAMOFFGROUP

09/2020 - up to date

DATA MANAGER

DATA MANAGER

CIO

EDUCATION

PUBLIC SCHOOL

2008 - 2016

BASIC EDUCATION

this school located in my hometown Sochi, i finished 11 classes with rate 4.4 (maximum is 5), this school is unique, because there are lots of English classes there.

UNIVERSITY OF RGU OIL AND GAS

2016 - 2020

BACHELOR'S DEGREE

My mean subject was manager in oil and gas companies. there were two mean modules of study, it was science of energy and science of working with people.

UNIVERSITY OF URGU OIL AND GAS

2020 - 2021

MASTER'S DEGREE

My mean subject was operator in oil and gas flows. But i do not completely finished my education because during Covid-19 the education was online and quality of it was awful.

CERTIFICATES

UDEMY

MAY 2022

GOOGLE

Feb 2022

REAKTOR

AUG 2021

FORAGE

AUG 2021

- CSS AND JAVASCRIPT CRASH COURSE
- ADVANCED GOOGLE ANALYTICS
- ELEMENTS OF AI
- ENGINEERING VIRTUAL PROGRAM